If you are seeing this video, you are
currently experiencing a Spore storm.
This is a newly occurring weather phenomenon.
Heavy clouds are approaching your location
carrying billions of mycopsychosis spores.
They travel through the air.
A single spore is enough to infect a host
Make sure you stay inside. Lock your doors and windows.
And don't exit under any circumstances.
Wait until the storm passes.
Try not to succumb to fear and wait patiently.
NOTE 10 [Noise] 0052440 to 0053440
How to identify the infection.
Mycopsychosis spores can enter your bloodstream through
your lungs, open cut or any exposed mucous membrane.
Symptoms only take a couple of minutes to appear.
Stages of the infection.
Stage One. General confussion.
The symptoms are sweating, fever, headache, vomit.
Once a host starts to develop these symptoms there is no possible cure.
NOTE 17 [Music] 0130120 to 0132320
Once a host starts to develop these symptoms, they should immediately
contact local Health authorities and wait for further instructions
Stage Two. Take over.
The symptoms are severe paranoia, visual and auditory
hallucinations, 'uncontrollably desire to socialize'.
The spores had arrived to the host's brain
and they are starting to take control.
NOTE 22 [Noise] 000202000 to 000202500
Stage Three. Activation
The symptoms are uncontrollably desired to go to a high place.
The spores had reproduced in the host body.
The infection has reached its maturity stage.
Stage Four. Blooming.
For further survivability please follow your Spore storm
survival manual, or check the following webpage.
NOTE 28 [Music] 000234500 to 000237000
NOTE 29 [Beep] 000237000 to 000242000